http://www.custom-seatcovers.com/legal.html

Seat Covers - Floor Mats - Dash Covers - Automotive Accessories
InstallationReturn Policy
(Click for Details)
The use of this site is governed by the policies, terms and conditions set forth below.
Please read them carefully. Your use of this site indicates your acceptance of these terms
and conditions. Your placement of an order indicates your acceptance of these terms and conditions.
EclipseCovers.com reserves the right to make changes to this site and these terms
and conditions at any time.
Privacy Policy
We keep your personal information
private and secure.
When you make a purchase from our site, you provide your name, email address,
credit card information, address, and phone number.
We only use this information to process your order.
We NEVER give this information to a third party.
Our secure servers protect the information using advanced encryption and firewall technology.
Your personal information cannot be read as it travels to our ordering system.
To keep you informed about our latest offers, we may notify you of current promotions, specials
and new additions to our site. You may unsubscribe from our newsletters by following the unsubscribe
instructions in any email you receive from us.
When entering any of our contests or prize drawings, you provide your name, email address and mailing
address. If you win, we will send the prize to the address entered and notify you by email.
When you enter a contest or drawing you are also included in our newsletter list to receive
notice of promotions, specials and new additions to our site. You may unsubscribe from this
news list by following the unsubscribe instructions in any email received.
We will never give or sell your personal information to third parties.
We do not use "cookies" or IP addresses to track your current shopping session.
If you purchase a gift certificate from our site, you will give us the recipient's name and
email address if you wish to send the certificate by email.
If we wish to send a certificate by
regular mail, you will give us the name, mailing information and phone number for the recipient.
The recipient information you give us will only be used to send the gift certificate and for no other
purpose.
Other sites accessible through our web site have their own privacy policies and data collection
practices.
Please consult each site's privacy policy.
We are not responsible for the actions of
third parties.
We fully cooperates with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for
illegal activities.
We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that
we reasonably believe to be unlawful.
Copyright Notice
This site is owned and operated by EclipseCovers.com.
Unless otherwise specified, all materials
appearing on this site, including the text, site design, logos, graphics, icons, and images,
as well as the selection, assembly and arrangement thereof, are the sole property of EclipseCovers.com
1998-2002, ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.
All software used on the
site is the sole property of EclipseCovers.com.
You may use the
content of this site only for the purpose of shopping on this site or placing an order on
this site and for no other purpose.
No materials from this site may be copied, reproduced,
modified, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted, or distributed in any form or by any
means without EclipseCovers.com prior written permission.
All rights not expressly granted
herein are reserved.
Any unauthorized use of the materials appearing on this site may violate
copyright, trademark and other applicable laws and could result in criminal or civil penalties.
Return Policy
By using this site and ordering from this site you agree to follow and abide by the return policy
described in detail in our Return Policy Page .
Disclaimer and Limitation of Liability as to Products Sold
All of EclipseCovers.com products are guaranteed against defects for 30 days from the date of the invoice.
Except as
expressly stated herein, EcliseCovers.com makes no representations or warranties, either express or implied, of any kind with respect
to products sold on the EclipseCovers.com sites. Except as expressly stated herein, EclipseCovers.com
expressly disclaims all warranties, express or implied, of any kind with respect to products sold on this site,
including but not limited to, merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose. You agree that the sole and exclusive
maximum liability to EclipseCovers.com arising from any product sold on our sites shall be the price
of the product ordered. In no event shall EclipseCovers.com, its directors, officers, employees or other representatives
be liable for special, indirect, consequential, or punitive damages related to product sold.
Disclaimer and Limitation of Liability as to the Custom-SeatCovers.com Web Sites
The Custom-SeatCovers.com web sites and the materials therein are provided as is. EclipseCovers.com makes no representations or
warranties, either express or implied, of any kind with respect to the Custom-SeatCovers.com sites, their operations, contents,
information, materials or year 2000 compliance. EclipseCovers.com expressly disclaims all warranties, express or implied,
of any kind with respect to the sites or their use, including but not limited to merchantability and fitness for a particular
purpose. You agree that EclipseCovers.com, its directors, officers, employees or other representatives shall not be
liable for damages arising from the operation, content or use of the Custom-SeatCovers.com sites. You agree that this
limitation of liability is comprehensive and applies to all damages of any kind, including without limitation
direct, indirect, compensatory, special, incidental, punitive and consequential damages.
Typographical Errors
In the event a product is listed at an incorrect price or with incorrect information due to typographical error or error in
pricing or product information received from our suppliers, EclipseCovers.com shall have the right to refuse or
cancel any orders placed for product listed at the incorrect price. Custom-SeatCovers.com shall have the
right to refuse or cancel any such orders whether or not the order has been confirmed and your
credit card charged. If your credit card has already been charged for the purchase and your
order is canceled, EclipseCovers.com shall immediately issue a credit to your credit card account in the
amount of the charge.
Links
This site may contain links to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by
third parties.
You acknowledge that EclipseCovers.com Inc. is not responsible for the operation of
or content located on or through any such site.
Order Acceptance Policy
Your receipt of an electronic or other form of order confirmation does not signify our acceptance of your
order, nor does it constitute confirmation of our offer to sell. Custom-SeatCovers.com reserves the right at any time
after receipt of your order to accept or decline your order for any reason. eclisecovers.com reserves the right at any time after receipt of your order, without prior notice to you, to supply less than the quantity
you ordered of any item. All orders placed over $ 800.00 (U.S.) must obtain pre-approval with an
acceptable method of payment, as established by our credit and fraud avoidance department.
We may require
additional verifications or information before accepting any order. Eclipsecovers.com is a reseller to end user
customers and does not accept orders from computer dealers, exporters, wholesalers, or other customers
who intend to resell the products offered by Custom-SeatCovers.com.
Sales Taxes
Custom-SeatCovers.com shall automatically charge and withhold the applicable sales tax for orders to be delivered to addresses within
Utah.
Each customer shall be solely responsible for all sales
taxes, or other taxes, on orders shipped to any other state.
Jurisdiction and Venue
You agree that any legal action brought against EclipseCovers.com shall be governed by the laws of the State of
Utah without regard to its conflict of law principles.
You agree that the sole jurisdiction and venue for
any litigation arising from your use of or orders made on the Custom-SeatCovers.com sites shall be an appropriate state
court located in Cache County Utah.
Custom SeatCoversinfo@Custom-SeatCovers.com
Copyright © 2010 Custom SeatCovers All rights reserved.     Terms of Use
